



# NARRA VENKATA RAGHU CHARAN-portfolio

GSSoC'23 Contributor. HacktoberFest Participant. Final-Year Computer Science and Engineering student with some hands-on experience in Machine Learning and Deep Learning. An inquisitive learner, determined individual and a passionate leader with an ambition to succeed and grow in any given environment.

## **EDUCATION**

### Gayatri Vidya Parishad College of Engineering (A)

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science and Engineering, 2020 - 2024

CGPA: 9.1

Intermediate Public Examination

Board of Intermediate of Education, Andhra Pradesh, 2018 - 2020

Percentage: 96.1%

**Secondary School Examination** 

Board of Secondary Education, 2008-2018

CGPA: 9.8

## **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: C, C++, Python, Java, R(basics)

Web Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript(Basics), Flask, MySQL(Basics), MongoDB(Basics)

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux(Ubuntu), Android

Soft skills: Leadership Skills, Networking, Problem-solving, Communication.

Frameworks and Tools: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Google Cloud, AWS, Android Studio, VS Code, Streamlit, Jupyter

#### **EXPERIENCE**

GDSC\_GVP - Google Cloud Campus Facilitator

08-09-2022 - April 2023.

Held Seminars on Cloud Computing.

Guided 50+ students in completion of GCCP.

Skills: Cloud Computing, GCP, Leadership skills

# GDG\_VIZAG - Core Volunteer

10-10-2022 - Present.

served as Core volunteer by hosting sessions on Cloud Computing and services provided by Google Cloud

Involved in event management of DevFest'22-Vizag

Skills: Problem-Solving, Organization of code fests, Event Management.

#### Google Developer Student Clubs\_GVP - Devops Lead

03-09-2022-April 2023.

Introduced the concept of DevOps and held some sessions on DevOps.

Hosted Hackathons

Skills: Leadership, Event management.

## **PROJECTS**

- Hand-Written Digit Recognition HandWritten Digit Recognition project is a web application that utilizes machine learning techniques to recognize and classify handwritten digits. code link
- Kovida (ML based WebApp) based on health conditions app gives personalized Insurance results.can be used by Insurance Companies. Tech Stack Used: Python, Streamlit. GitHub Link.
- Signature Verfication using DTW A Streamlit App to verify authenticity of signatures of users. Github\_Link.

## **CERTIFICATES & BADGES**

- Google Cloud Career Practitioner
- **AWS Cloud Foundations**
- Hacker Rank (Python)
- Google Developer Profile (Android with Kotlin)
- 30 Days of Google Cloud

#### **HOBBIES**

- Writes At Hashnode
- Blogging (Reading Articles in Medium, TowardsDatascience,)
- Sports

## **LANGUAGES**

- **English**
- Hindi
- Telugu

